

RAFAEL MORALES

Digital Marketer International MBA in Digital Marketing

PERSONAL HISTORY

Professional with a total of 7 years of work experience. More than 3 years of experience in the technology industry and 2 years working in digital marketing, leading eCommerce projects, website development, design and execution of SEO, social media management and inbound marketing strategies.

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- SEO & SEM
- · Inbound Marketing
- · Analytics & Monitoring
- · Remarketing

PLATFORMS AND TOOLS

- Google (Analytics + Ads + Tag Manager)
- Google (Merchant Center + Console)
- WordPress + WooCommerce
- Facebook Ads / Store + Wapp Business

WORK EXPERIENCE

SEO & eCommerce Manager Freelance

Active Visions Group | Jan 2020 - Present

- Creation, management and execution of SEO strategy.
- Creation of the eCommerce site through WordPress and Woocommerce.
- Design and execution of inbound marketing strategy.

Digital Marketing Manager Freelance

Iluminar | 11/2018 - Present

- Increased repeat buying from 10% to 35%.
- Achieved a 300% ROI digital marketing conversion campaigns.
- Sales margin improved by 22% after implementation of online sales channels and inbound marketing strategies.

BI Consultant

Zeus Tecnología | Jun 2015 - Oct 2018

- Development of the financial panel to end-user increased the license acquisition of BI department by 25%.
- Elaborated more than 60 personalized ad-hoc reports to customers from different industries: hospitality, retail, manufacturing, health, travel, etc.

CONTACT INFO

WhatsApp: <u>+57 3052661440</u> rafaelmorales112@hotmail.com Current Location: Bogotá, Colombia

My Portfolio

EDUCATION

M.Sc. International MBA

ESIC Business & Marketing School - SISU | 2018 - 2020

M.sc. Tax Managemet

Universidad Tecnológica | 2017 - 2018

B.Sc. Business Administrator

Universidad del Norte | 2009 - 2014